

# Jordi Altayó González

Electrical Engineer

I am a 22-year-old Electrical Engineering student passionate about technology. My career goal is to gain experience in all facets of Engineering and move towards Microelectronic Design. I am also a musician with interests in Art and Philosophy.

#### Education

2012-2014 High School, Sagrada Família, Sabadell.

Technological modality. See diploma.

2014–2018 Electrical Engineering B.Sc, UPC-ETSETB, Barcelona.

Electronics track. 240 ECTS.

2018–2020 Embedded Systems M.Sc, KTH, Stockholm.

Embedded Electronics track. 120 ECTS

2002–2016 Musical Education, Professional Conservatory, Sabadell.

- o Main instrument: viola.
- o Secondary instruments: piano and trombone.
- o Others: composer and arranger.

## Experience

2014–2018 Private teacher.

Maths, Physics and Electronics teacher for high-shcool-level students.

2015–2018 Musician, Simfònica de Cobla i Corda de Catalunya, Girona.

Titular violist. Participated in various award-wining CD recordings such as *Tossudament Llach*, *Cançó d'Amor i de Guerra* and *The Very Best*.

2015–2018 Musician, Eiron Quintet, Sabadell.

Founder and member of the group.

Feb-Jul **R&D Intern**, eSilicon, Barcelona.

2018 Development of a metric analysis tool for ASIC HLBs under Synopsys PrimeTime and ICC2 environments as part of an internship and the Bachelor's Degree Thesis. This tool will allow designers to have a quick overview on all aspects of the block during the design process without the need to deepen into the design and potentially lose time by analyzing useless or redundant data. It will also provide reports with design changes proposals (ECO) to either facilitate timing closure or reduce power consumption.

#### Courses, awards and recognitions

October Composition Contest, Professional Conservatory, Sabadell.

2015 Jury award for the piece "Quartet de Tardor". See diploma.

October Innovate or Die<sup>†</sup>, LEINN, Barcelona.

2016 Second place at the challange of Pyrum®. See diploma.

October Composition Contest, Professional Conservatory, Sabadell.

2016 Jury and public award for the piece "Petit Príncep". See diploma.

November **EBEC**<sup>†</sup>, *B.E.S.T.*, Barcelona.

2016 Winner of the Regional edition. See diploma.

April 2017 **EBEC**<sup>†</sup>, *B.E.S.T.*, Valladolid.

Finalist of the National edition. See diploma.

†EBEC stands for European B.E.S.T. (Board of European Students of Technology) Engineering Competition. It is a contest where participants are given 48 hours to solve a challenge by designing and building a functional prototype with the resources provided by the organizers.

PrimeTime

IC Compiler II

Design Compiler

Cadence Virtuoso

Altium Designer

GNU/Linux Git/SVN

ATEX

Driving license

Own car

LabVIEW (CLAD)

Sept-Dec CBI Course, UPC & CERN, Barcelona & Geneva.

2017 Operational methods for radiation inspection project. See dioploma.

March Hackathon Mobility, SEAT & CARNET, Barcelona.

2018 First place at SEAT challange: Al for Mobility & Driving Experience. See prize and video.

### Languages

Spanish Native

Catalan Native

English C1 (IELTS) See certificate
French B2 (DELF) See certificate

#### Personal Skills

Programming Languages Hardware Languages Software

PythonMATLABVerilogVHDL

• C/C++ • SystemVerilog

o Tcl/Tk o Verilog A/AMS

o Bash

Soft Skills Others

Multidisciplinary team-work capabilities

Ability to adapt to changes in undergoing projects

Excellent communication skills

Ability to analyze and solve complex problems

## **Projects**

December Ultrasound distance meter, UPC, Barcelona.

2015 Project developed in a group of 4 engineers. Report can be downloaded here.

December **Design of a Class-D audio amplifier**, *UPC*, Barcelona.

2016 Project developed in a group of 4 engineers. Report can be downloaded here.

June 2017 **Autonomous weather-related measurement adquisition system**, *UPC*, Barcelona.

Project developed in a group of 2 engineers. Report can be downloaded here.

December CBI Course, UPC & CERN, Barcelona & Geneva.

2017 Project developed in a student team of 2 engineers, 2 designers and 2 MBAs. Final dossier can be downloaded here.

June 2018 Bachelor's Thesis, eSilicon & UPC, Barcelona.

Improving ASIC HLBs Quality of Results Using Design Metrics. See Experience for Project details.

March Design of a SAR ADC, Stokholm.

2019 Design of a 5-bit SAR ADC operating at 100 MHz. See report here.

Ongonig KTH Formula Student, UPC, Stokholm.

Member of the low-voltage electronics group. See website here.